onlinenic.com 2019-05-08

# OnlineNIC PRIVACY Policy

                OnlineNIC PRIVACY Policy
ONLINENIC INC (ONLINENIC) TAKES YOUR PRIVACY SERIOUSLY.
Our Privacy Policy is intended to describe to you how and what data we collect, and how and
why we use your personal data. It also describes options we provide for you to access, update
or otherwise take control of your personal data that we process. Your privacy is very important
to us. We do not sell any personal data of our customers to another company for marketing
purposes.
By “personal information”, we mean information that could include such as: name, address,
telephone number, date of birth, Email address, Credit card number, and other data collected
that could directly or indirectly identify you.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR PRIVACY
By using our services (the “Services”) you agree to the use, collection and disclosure of the
data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all
users, members registered with us.
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
OnlineNIC collects personal information in accordance with requirements or technical standard
by domain’s registries and ICANN. In most instances, you provide the information directly to
OnlineNIC Inc, such as when you create an Account, sign up for a newsletter, purchase
OnlineNIC’s services, or request further information from us.
SIGN-UP FOR SERVICES
    Information you provide in any registration process, such as your email, name, mailing
     address when you provide it to us;
    Information that you provide during any registration process (such as your name,
     company name, email address, phone number, billing address or credit card information,
     geographic location and industry), when you call or email us (for support or otherwise) or
     when you use our products or services; and
    Payment information that you provide to us (by way of our Services or otherwise) when
     you purchase some of our products and services, including credit card data.

USE OF OUR SERVICES
    Information you provide when you contact our support for assistance;
    Information you provide when you participate in marketing program and surveys, or
     otherwise participate in activities we promote that might require information about you.
    Information you provide during your interactions with our website such as social media
     features or other similar widgets.
    Information you provide for DOMAIN REGISTRATION SERVICES (DOMAIN
     REGISTRATION SERVICES PRIVACY POLICY ADDENDUM is part of this privacy
     policy) or other service/products we provide.
OTHER RESOURCES
    Information that is publicly available; and
    Information you consent to us receiving from third parties.
COOKIES and TRACKING
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP
address, operating system and browser type in order to administer our website, to
customize your experience, to temporarily record session information and/or to assist you
in browsing the site. This may in some instances only be statistical data about how you
browse our site.
We use cookies on this site to:
    improve your experience on our site
    save your preferences and login information, and to provide personalized functionality
    “required cookies” are necessary for our website to work properly, understand your usage
     of our site
    help identify you and maintain your signed-in status
    measure the effectiveness of our advertising
    provide more focused marketing communications to you
         .
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser. However, if you
select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have
adjusted your browser so that it will refuse cookies, our system could issue cookies when you
log on to our site.
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

  We use the information we collect both on its own and combined with any other
  information we collect about you, for the purposes that may include, but not limited to, the
  following:
 To communicate with you. The contacts may include: Email, Telephone calls, mail
  address, etc.
 To comply with legal, regulatory and law enforcement requests.
  We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to
  enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to
  government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion,
  believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (such as
  subpoena requests), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third
  party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we
  consider to be illegal or unethical.
 To comply with ICANN or any TLDs’ rules, regulations and policies.
 To share with trusted third parties who provide services such as payment processing,
  order fulfilment, customer service, website hosting, data analysis, infrastructure provision,
  IT services, email delivery services, auditing services and other similar services to enable
  them to provide services.
 To share with THIRD PARTY VENDORS, include serving advertisements, conducting
  survey, and website analytics companies such as Google Analytics. We use the
  information provided by these vendors to improve services on this site. These partners
  and vendors use cookies, web beacons and other technologies such as tags and scripts
  to collect information about your online activity (e.g., the sites and pages you have visited
  at the site and at times other 3rd party sites) in order to: help manage ad campaigns,
  understand user interests and trends and deliver personalized content and advertising to
  you while you are on the site or on other sites. Each cookie cannot be used by anyone
  other than the service provider. OnlineNIC's websites is currently using Google Analytics,
  which is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"), to evaluate your use
  of the OnlineNIC’s website. Google Analytics place a third-party cookie on your computer
  that is then used to compile reports of visitor traffic and internet usage. Google Analytics
  does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor and only collects aggregate
  data. For information on how Google Analytics uses data please visit “How Google uses
  data when you use our partners sites or apps”, located at
  www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can prevent Google Analytics from
  recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling the Google Analytics cookie on
  your browser.
 To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment,
  transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including
  in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). Any prospective purchasers or
  new owners will be similarly bound by this Privacy Statement.
 To share with a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture,
  assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or

      stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). Any
      prospective purchasers or new owners will be similarly bound by this Privacy Statement.
     The AUTHORIZED USERS that have access to your account can view personal
      information stored in the account. A primary account holder can view personal information
      saved in subaccounts to which they have authorized access. We share information about
      authorized users only for legitimate purposes consistent with this privacy policy, including
      servicing your account and marketing products and services to you.
     We also share non-personal information that does not reveal your specific identity, such
      as:
      Browser information
      Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies such as scripts
      Demographic information and other information provided by you
      Aggregated information) with certain third parties
OnlineNIC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third-party sites linked
in our website or any own-managed applications. Please read the privacy policy of any website
you visit.
SECURITY
OnlineNIC do our best to protect data under control. The technical security measures include
but not limited to: physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the
information we collect online. When we collect financial account information, such as credit
card numbers, we protect its transmission through the use of encryption such as the Transport
Layer Security (TLS) protocol.
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
For purposes of the US COPPA laws, we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from
visitors under the age of 13. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13, we will
terminate any account that user may have with us and will delete any Personal Information
that they have submitted from our records.
YOUR RIGHTS
If your information changes, or discontinue your services with us and/or unsubscribe our
marketing communications, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove
that your personal data in our records.
You have the right to know whether we process personal information about you, and if we do,
to access data we hold about you and certain information about how we use it and who we

share it with. You also have the right to access your Personal Information, the right to correct
any inaccuracies in the details we hold about you.
You may send your request to us via email address onlinenic-enduser@onlinenic.com.
RESELLERS
In addition to all of the terms and conditions set forth above, the following terms apply to
OnlineNIC’s resellers.
We may collect information under the direction of our Resellers, but we have no direct
relationship with the our Resellers’ client, customers or users (“end user”) or the personal data
provided, processed or obtained by our Resellers. Reseller Users should direct all queries to
the Reseller.
If end user doesn’t want to be contacted by such Reseller, he/she should contact his/her
Reseller.
We retain personal data we process on behalf of our Resellers for as long as needed to
provide services under the relationship. We will retain, use and disclose this personal
information as necessary
     To comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements
     To disclose information to service providers and for domain registration and legal and
      compliance reasons.
RETENTION PERIOD
We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined
in this Privacy Statement, such as legitimate interest in maintaining the information, law
requirement, and regulatory compliance, etc.
PRIVACY UPDATE
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this
privacy policy in any material way, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on
our website. Your use of the site following these changes means that you accept the revised
Privacy Statement.
CONTACT US

If you have any questions, concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via Email:
onlinenic-enduser@onlinenic.com, or fax +1-510-769-8487
We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

    DOMAIN REGISTRATION SERVICES PRIVACY POLICY ADDENDUM
The following privacy policy addendum, together with the OnlineNIC’s privacy policy (the
“Privacy Policy”), is applicable to you if you purchased domain registration services from
OnlineNIC Inc (“we,” “us” or “OnlineNIC”). Please review the below in addition to the Privacy
Policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
When you purchase Domain Registration services for top level domains (“TLDs”), as the
domain registrar, we are required to collect the following personal information from you
(collectively, “Personal Information”):
            Registrant Name
            Registrant Organization (where applicable)
            Registrant Address
            Registrant Email
            Registrant Fax (where applicable)
            Registrant Phone number
            Administrative Contact
            Administrative Contact Organization (where applicable)
            Administrative Contact Address
            Administrative Contact Email
            Administrative Contact Fax (where applicable)
            Administrative Contact Telephone Number
            Technical Contact
            Technical Contact Organization (where applicable)
            Technical Contact Address
            Technical Contact Email
            Technical Contact Fax (where applicable)
            Technical Contact Telephone Number
            Billing Contact
            Billing Contact Organization (where applicable)
            Billing Contact Address
            Billing Contact Email
            Billing Contact Fax (where applicable)
            Billing Contact Telephone Number
Our collection of Personal Information is necessary to comply with contractual obligations we
have with the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers (“ICANN”) and with
certain TLD registries (“Registries”) so that you can validly register your domain name. In
addition to Personal Information, our contracts with some Registries may require us to collect

other personal information for the registration of a TLD such as certain professional affiliations,
identification or other qualifiers (“Additional Personal Information”).
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
        Public Whois. Our contracts with ICANN and other Registries require us to make
         certain domain name information (“WHOIS Information”) available and accessible to
         the public through a searchable port 43 “WHOIS” Service via a public webpage
         operated by the applicable registrar of record (“WHOIS site”). The WHOIS site is a
         publicly accessible database that lists WHOIS Information, including a particular
         domain name, the name server(s) to which the domain name points, and the domain
         name’s creation and expiration date. Except for EU/EEA natural persons (as described
         below), your Personal Information could be displayed on the WHOIS site.
        EU/EEA natural persons. Notwithstanding the foregoing, pursuant to the European
         Union’s General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679, or GDPR, if you are a EU/EEA
         natural person (as defined by the GDPR), other than as specified in this addendum,
         our publication of WHOIS Information will not contain any Personal Information.
         Accordingly, we will not display Personal Information of an EU/EEA natural person on
         the WHOIS site unless you explicitly opt out of this protection.
        Transfer Out. If you initiate a transfer out of a domain name away from us as the
         registrar of record, pursuant to our contract with ICANN, we may need to publish your
         registrant email address obtained from your Personal Information on the WHOIS site
         for a period of approximately five (5) calendar days. After this period and assuming a
         valid transfer has occurred, you would cease to be our customer for that domain name
         and your WHOIS Information would be managed by the gaining registrar.
        Certain Registries. Registries are third party providers of TLDs that are independent
         of domain registrars. If required by contract with a particular Registry, we may be
         obligated, as a domain registrar of domains provided by the Registry, to provide
         Personal Information and Additional Personal Information to such Registry to
         successfully complete your domain name registration. If we provide your Personal
         Information and Additional Personal Information to a Registry, the Registry has its own
         obligation to comply with applicable data privacy laws.
        Data Escrow. Our contract with ICANN requires us to deposit the Personal
         Information collected with a secure third-party escrow provider who acts solely as a
         holder of the data.
        Permitted Disclosures. We may also disclose your Personal Information when
         required by the rules, regulations and policies of ICANN, including but not limited to
         the Uniform Domain-Name Dispute-Resolution Policy (UDRP).
